I've been up here for too long, Winters and I still can't make sense of the nuke.
Take this ruckus.
It started with one of their shamans.
Maria, spouting on about spirits.
Set Damon's up on thunder drum.
So they marched their way Eric up there and half of them get started by machines.
I don't know what Aurea found up there.
A shaman is not going to talk to an out.
The machines in the cut are getting more vicious.
That's a fact.
It could be because of the Daimon.
Oh, it could be because they all got indigestion for all I know.
But it really is not around to explain.
She took off dot thought that crazy might have gone with her
out again.
Maybe I can get back inside to that structure over there.
Looks like you need to get to those stairs.
Yeah,
no
precise before even breathe out,
you know, much higher to climb.
Maria must be close.
She has to be in here somewhere,
you know.
Okay.
Someone had the menu board to display of scene messages about our colleague.
Mr Blevins.
Is this the most advanced geological project ever undertaken, or a junior high locker room.
Come on, people.
No,
I ask again as I've asked 1000 times.
Speak to me.
One more Would you have me do?
Is there no prayer that will reach you?
No, Mark, That will break your bonds.
I can't help you if you won't speak
whispers all I ask.
Guide me.
Who?
No How
How did you get here?
The way was sealed by the spirit herself.
I
I used one of these.
I could show you.
Yes, Show me,
please.
But the goals the same.
Get the light back to the source.
Channel recovered.
Exploit successfully restraints evaded.
Is someone there in Korea?
Korea?
No, I will not submit.
You brought.
You heard it.
The voice of the spirit calling to me from the heights of Thunders Drum.
She was able to throw off the bonds of the Daimon for a moment because of what you did.
Who are you
and what do you want?
I'm a Loy now.
Took sent me.
He thought that you could use my help.
He was not mistaken.
You've been a
revelation.
Now I know for certain that the spirit endures.
Perhaps together we can find a way to set her free.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
I came all this way for answers, and so far I haven't heard any.
It seems to me that you are the answer, but of course I'll tell you while I can, Bergrin said.
You might know something about a man named Silence that you may have had dealings with him at the conclave.
When that name is spoken secret.
Soon follow or vanish as the case may be.
Why did you want to know?
He's put me in danger but also offered help.
I don't know as much about him as I'd like.
Tio, I would imagine his aide is very powerful.
It will not come without cost.
Unfortunately, I am sworn to an oath of secrecy by the conclave on this matter.
I get that.
But you and I are trying to help each other, right?
Yes, but I would be breaking an oath and that
I cannot do about silence.
I've told you all I can.
There's nothing more I can say.
He seemed to have a history with this voice.
This spirit she saved my life
here years ago, during the war with the Kasia,
a raid scattered my work I was cut off alone
I lured the enemy into the rhyme drifts hoping to lose them in the mist.
But they endured So I took refuge In this case
that's when I heard a voice
I wonder Lost like me Spirit of the blue Like it's under from it She asked me for aid.
She chose me but I was in no position to help.
Not with the cars after May.
So she helped me first
by closing the door on the mountain below When you must have opened to get here locked by means similar to those found in this room
it kept the cars are from reaching me safe from them
I was able to do Is she asked what did the spirit want from you?
She said she was hurt incomplete.
She needed bones parts not unlike what you'd find in machine.
They were here in this room.
She wanted me to bring them to Thunders Drum.
So I did and she showed me how to heal her.
So began our communion.
Inside thunders drum is a room like this one only larger with an altar I went there many times to speak with her.
What did she say?
She told me she was lost and needed my help.
She asked questions about our lands, our tribe.
And she listened with patients with wisdom.
I told her things Long kept silent about my family, my dreams, my fears.
She never tired of me.
Never judged.
We kept each other's company.
Maria,
what do you think?
The Spiritus I see
You are not a nuke on our songs.
They're not familiar to you.
You did not know of blue light that which struggles to survive in our hearts and animates the machines the essence of life and in its purest form,
harmony.
As the anger of the machines grows, this light has faded from the world and the spirits it sustains are stranded.
That's what she is.
A lost soul cut off from what it needs.
Lonely, forsaken.
I must help her way Must I'm not sure if I understand,
but I want Teo.
That's all I need.
The Damon.
What do you know about it?
I spoke with the spirit many times.
First here, then inside Thunders Drum.
The last time
she told me she was under attack by something that could not be seen by mortal eyes, something evil.
She named it Damon and said it needed her power to do what it wilt.
And she begged me for help, to find a way to destroy her if necessary, to keep it from using her.
That was five years ago.
I didn't hear her voice again until today.
What kept you from the spirit?
After it begs for help?
I went to our talk hoping he could protect her.
But the war with the cars just still raged.
And before I could reach him
I was ambushed by the Madsen King's Kestral Tze and taken to Meridian in chains.
I wasn't able to return to Thunder Strom until long after the liberation.
Not until last thought that was the expedition that went bad.
I saw the funeral
Yes,
once there was finally peace with Cardassia Our attack and I gathered a work of great hunters to defeat the demon.
And yet the old door to thunders drum was con replaced by a gate.
We could not pass many machines.
We were crushed
our top called a retreat.
But we had already lost our best.
We abandoned them to the snow as we fell back
after,
you know, I could not agree on what to do next.
So I came here hoping against hope, to hear the spirit again.
And because of you,
I did whatever this Damon is, it's related to the machines and why they've become more dangerous.
I want to know how
both the spirit and the Damon or on a mountain thunder strum So why don't we go there and figure out what it all means?
We camped thunders Drum is dangerous More than you can imagine.
The Damon has secured it.
Besides,
our talk won't let us go as chieftain he controls the past to the mountain.
Then he can't be reasoned with sounds like you need a new chieftain.
There's an idea that's certain to win us friends
You said you were a hunter
and I'll wager you're not an ordinary one.
It's not impossible even for an Outlander And our attack couldn't refuse the challenge if you were known among the way rock Wait uh me challenge our talk
I don't want to be chieftain of anything much less a bunch of eunuch that don't want me But you want to go to Thunders drum Don't you.
You heard the spirit.
She's suffering.
Tormented by the Damon, she longs to be free.
And perhaps when released from her bombs, she can give you the answers you seek.
I can't believe I'm agreeing to this.
Fine.
What do I have to dio?
Get the way, Rex Attention To show the worth of your claim.
Win at the hunting grounds.
Kill bandits.
The prey on the cut.
They don't dare talk.
The great were acts of gun or to the north.
But the cut is easier prey.
A rogue awesome has equipped a gang in the plume lands with strange new gear.
Just the kind of thing you seem to make sense of winning at the hunting grounds will impress the way Eric Alba Nuke strive to be the best.
For our harsh lands were very pretenders in the ice.
And so the hunting grounds in the snow chances a great boon place to hone our spears and sharpen our aim.
Tell a book keeper there and I sent you.
If you best the mark of one of the champions she trained, it will impress the where I indeed has our talking to react to being challenged by an Outlander about as well as you'd expect.
But let me handle that.
When the time comes for you to throw your spirit, our talks feat, I will be there to back your claim.
I'll see you later, show when the time is right.
Oh, and one more thing in the box over there is a weapon like my own.
You may find it useful.
May our pilgrimage to thunders drum succeed.
Yeah,
it's a figure of must have been an ancient animal.
Kenny and I don't need to fight about the laundry.
So instead, we fight about in commence ability and restrictions on machine intelligence.
You might regret this.
Okay.
I can't feel my I can't do much of anything in this,
You know,
I'd have to ditch something.
I can't get out of this.
I'll get you
hunting grounds.
Go to places.
I need to make a name for myself with the nuke
keeper.
Aria said that I should compete in the trials here.
Gloria did.
She's never sent someone before.
And what is your reason for training?
I would ask this of any minute who attempted the trial's im going to challenge our talk to become chieftain of his work.
Well, you better get started then you look like you've got some storeys to tell.
No, I lived most of my storeys
Iran with the thunders daughter's long ago before they run their course For a time we shook the snow off.
The men have been our
I couldn't last Some fill in glorious battle somewhere exiled in infamy Still glorious if you ask me.
Others had a worse fate.
What's worse, to grow old?
We find that all the rules and traditions you fought so hard against are still there.
That's why I tell all the hunters are trying to stay young.
I'm guessing you're not part of the hunter's lodge.
Every tribe claims they were the first to have hunting grounds.
Then every tribe claims the car just stole it from them.
So who was the first?
We were and the car just old from you.
That's right.
How did the trials work around here?
There's no car, Jim medals.
I had some, but I used them to patch up holes in my snow boots.
Instead, you compete against the best time set by other BA nuke hunters to take second place.
Even third place puts you among names of legend.
What if I come in first?
We'll see.
So you'll need to own a BA nuke storm slinger to take this trial.
No more trials?
Not yet.
You can always come back.
You got determination that can't be taught.
The control trial tests the hunters ability to rein in the storm's lingers power.
Only the wisest understand these demonic weapons and only the bravest Well, hm.
Use the rope to get to the arena and we'll start.
All right.
What?
Yeah,
I thought they go on forever.
I need them soon enough.
Your first run on that trial.
And you claimed second place.
I haven't seen many.
Pull that off.
The owns lot trial challenges a hunter to withstand the ebb and flow of combat.
Machines will be released into the arenas in waves.
Pace yourself.
Strategise.
Only then will you be able to defeat them all without being overwhelmed.
All right,
that's coming with me.
Your first run on that trial and you claimed second place.
I haven't seen many pull that off.
This trial is the most dangerous ordeal in the snow.
Chance.
Well, not all chieftains pass it.
Only a chieftain may attempt it.
I'm done with training right now.
Training's done with you.
I beat a champion's time that should get the wear act talking.
You know,
thiss may be my last record in a cold and friendless land interiors, I admit my mistake following in the well travelled our arms footsteps, lacking his experience or snowshoes.
Yet I had always dreamed of seeing the land of the book for myself.
For my folly.
I have been buffeted by blizzards, chased by machines and presto what must be the very gates of Banner.
I trust there watch towers above and that the nuke will not leave a traveller to his death.
But the wind drowns out my calls for aid, and any sign I make is fast extinguished.
My only hope is to huddle here and wait for a break in the snow even as I hear my pursuers drawing ever closer.
Osan should this be the end?
See to it that my worldly possessions are distributed equally among my five cousins, and my flower garden and bright market is watered regularly twice daily for the rest Sounds in my memory.
December 23rd 2046 Subject.
First stage of main facility.
Complete attention, all staff.
It's with pride that I announce the completion of the first level of infrastructure in our primary facility.
This compound will be the nerve centre for our project and will require the teams continued best efforts to realise by the deadline.
But even though there is much more to be done, you should be pleased with all you've accomplished so far.
Please find attached to detailed plan for mustering out of the auxiliary space, which will serve as a contingency site.
As we proceed with the main facility, 90% of our personnel must be relocated by 5 p.m. Wednesday.
If your name does not appear on the assignment list, please email Marissa with me and see see your dedication, Talent and intelligence remain daily sources of inspiration.
Dr.
Kenny Chow, project director.
NPF from Kenny Chow BCC Don BLEVINS Date.
December 3rd 2046 Subject.
Attacking of many aboard Attention all staff at an assembly of our country's finest scientific minds.
Recruited to address a grave threat to national safety, it would be fair to expect more mature conduct than that demonstrated yesterday in the canteen.
Mr.
Blevins plays a crucial role in the successful execution of Fire Break and is due the respect both of his title and of his many contributions to the project.
Any further interference in the menu boards will necessitate my direct personal involvement.
Dr.
Kenny Chow, project director from Penny Chow to Anita Sandoval.
Date.
December 3rd 2046 Subject.
Forward Hacking of Menu Board.
Anita Was you smile.
I need a Sandoval.
A personal log.
I had an argument with Kenny this afternoon when a couple's first fight hinges on the touring act.
You know you're dealing with some real sexy nerds.
I won the argument, I guess, but I'm less concerned whether or not I can pull this off.
Then, with the ethical implications of succeeding, I promised Kenny that the suite of coping mechanism side design will help manage any emotional fallout from the software.
But privately, I'm less confident I'm a programmer, not a shrink.
The minutia robo ethics do start to seem less relevant when a refusal to supply fire break with the necessary conditions for its success comes at the cost of millions of lives.
It's worth putting one consciousness at risk to save so many others, isn't it?
Trying to solve this with numbers makes me feel like a sociopath